http://www.atatrail.org/about-us/terms-and-conditions-of-use

GREAT ALLEGHENY PASSAGE ®
150 miles of biking and hiking from Cumberland, MD to Pittsburgh, PA
EXPLORE THE TRAIL
Terms and Conditions of Use
Permission is granted to temporarily download information on Allegheny Trail Alliance's web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing or use only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Allegheny Trail Alliance ‘s website;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Allegheny Trail Alliance at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
Disclaimer
The materials on Allegheny Trail Alliance's web site are provided "as is". Allegheny Trail Alliance makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Allegheny Trail Alliance does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
Limitations
In no event shall Allegheny Trail Alliance or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Allegheny Trail Alliance's Internet site, even if Allegheny Trail Alliance or an Allegheny Trail Alliance authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on Allegheny Trail Alliance's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Allegheny Trail Alliance does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Allegheny Trail Alliance may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Allegheny Trail Alliance does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
Links
Allegheny Trail Alliance has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Allegheny Trail Alliance of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.
Site Terms of Use Modifications
Allegheny Trail Alliance may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
Governing Law
Any claim relating to Allegheny Trail Alliance's web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Pennsylvania without regard to its conflict of law provisions.General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
GAP
The Great Allegheny Passage ® (GAP) rail-trail offers 150 miles of hiking and biking from Cumberland MD to Pittsburgh,PA.
WANT TO HELP?
Volunteer
Donate
